{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","address":"8825 E Jefferson Ave","zipcode":"48214","owner":"ECS Partnership","licenseNumber":"043508","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"6/6/2017","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E61000000CB0420934BF54C018F7F887A42D4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44307","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","inspectionDate":"2018-11-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44307","inspectionDate":"11/30/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"Floor(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"44307","inspectionDate":"11/30/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"water line(s)","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"At the Mop sink","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"44307","inspectionDate":"11/30/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing Test strips","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"44307","inspectionDate":"11/30/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Sink","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"44307","inspectionDate":"11/30/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Shake machine","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"40944","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","inspectionDate":"2017-11-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40944","inspectionDate":"11/30/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"At the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"40944","inspectionDate":"11/30/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"40944","inspectionDate":"11/30/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Inside the Walk-in freezer","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"40944","inspectionDate":"11/30/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT PREP AREA","subLocation":"Inside the Shake machine","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"40944","inspectionDate":"11/30/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"BREAK ROOM","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"37472","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","inspectionDate":"2016-12-22T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint/Routine","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37472","inspectionDate":"12/22/2016","inspectionType":"Complaint/Routine","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"doors","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"REAR AREA","subLocation":"At the Ice machine","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"37472","inspectionDate":"12/22/2016","inspectionType":"Complaint/Routine","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Plumbing","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-01-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"37472","inspectionDate":"12/22/2016","inspectionType":"Complaint/Routine","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"4-903.12","violationDescription":"Cleaned and SANITIZED EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES  shall be stored only in approved locations.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored","subProblem":"In toilet room","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"At the Unused equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove and store in protected area."},{"inspectionid":"37472","inspectionDate":"12/22/2016","inspectionType":"Complaint/Routine","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-01-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"37472","inspectionDate":"12/22/2016","inspectionType":"Complaint/Routine","establishmentid":"2370","name":"McDonald's #2285","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"REAR AREA","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-12-22T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2370"}}